hey0.net 2011-12-10

# Lithium Hosting - Lithium Hosting Privacy Policy

Lithium Hosting Privacy Policy

  1. **Privacy Of Your Payment Details**

We use encrypted SSL connection to process your credit card information and DO NOT store any of your payment details in our system. The payments are carried out in the background by the Quantum Gateway processing system and go through CDG Commerce's terminal. Working with a reliable online credit card merchant, we guarantee fast and secure processing of your payment. Not only do we NOT make a record of your credit card details in our system, but also - for maximum online security - we do NOT share this information with any third party.

  2. **Privacy Of Your Account**

We consider your registration data and the content of all your messages private and confidential. The header of the messages that you send will contain your name (e-mail address) and Internet Protocol (IP) address. We will not intentionally monitor or disclose any of your e-mail content or registration data unless we are required to do so:

    * to enforce these Terms and Conditions,
    * by law,
    * to defend ourselves in any legal action,
    * to protect our property.

Since your password is essential for protecting your privacy, we encourage you to NOT share it with anyone and change it frequently. Additionally, you agree to respect the privacy and confidentiality of others.

  3. **Privacy Of Your Registration Data**

Lithium Hosting collects certain information during the registration process. The personally identifiable information that Lithium Hosting collects includes first and last name. Lithium Hosting also collects non-personally identifiable information, such as country, age, gender, etc. You may update your Registration Information at any time from the Client Area \- > My Details - > Change Password section.

Lithium Hosting will keep the personally identifiable information of all Customers private and confidential, and will NOT share it with any unauthorized third parties. We may disclose aggregate registration statistics in connection with our marketing activities.

  4. **Why We Need This Information**

Your registration information is needed in order for us to operate the site, to provide support for your account, for statistical purposes, etc. Lithium Hosting will NOT send you any unsolicited information, including e-mails, except as mentioned hereby.

New customers will receive a Lithium Hosting welcome e-mail containing information about the features provided by the Service, as well as cPanel (Client Area) and FTP login details. Lithium Hosting may also send system notifications upon need, related to any upgrade, maintenance or other service issues concerning your hosting account.

Lithium Hosting will keep your personally identifiable information private and will NOT share it with any unauthorized third parties.
